sportgfx.com 2010-06-12

# Privacy Statement - Sport GFX Forum

## **Intro**

**SportGFX.com** is an online community that aims to provide the best graphics and football resources, news and products to people from all over the world. The agreement on this site is between you and SportGFX.com.

Forum posts and users may be banned from this site, without prior warning or explanation, at the sole discretion of SportGFX.com Staff.

* * *

### **Acceptance of Agreement**

When you visit this or become a member of the forums, you accept this Agreement. This Agreement may be updated from time to time, so make sure you read through it every now and then. If any part of this Agreement or updates to these Agreements are not acceptable to you, you may cancel your account and stop visiting this site. The use of this site and our forums means that you agree with the Agreement.

Registration to this forum is free! We do insist that you abide by the rules and policies detailed below. If you agree to the terms, please check the ’I agree’ checkbox and press the ’Register’ button below. If you would like to cancel the registration, click [here](http://sportgfx.com/forum/) to return to the forums index.

Although the administrators and moderators of SportGFX will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off this forum, it is impossible for us to review all messages. All messages express the views of the author, and neither the administrators, moderators, or owners of SportGFX will be held responsible for the content of any message.

By agreeing to these rules, you warrant that you will not post any messages that are obscene, vulgar, sexually-oriented, hateful, threatening, or otherwise violative of any laws.

The owners of SportGFX reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any thread for any reason.

* * *

### **Rules**

We would like to thank you for taking the time to read the following rules of SportGFX. These rules are plain and simple, so if you just follow them, there will be no problems!

  * **No swearing or abusive language** \- We don't tolerate racism, sexism, homophobia, ageism or other forms of hate-speech or content that could be interpreted as such. Don't post messages that are unlawful, harassing, defamatory, abusive, threatening, harmful, obscene, profane, sexually oriented or racially offensive. Please don't use language people may find offensive.

  * **No Piracy** \- This includes ANY discussion, mentioning of warez, crack, hacking, or ANY software, method, and sites connected to them.

  * **No pornography** \- No pornography in posts, sigs, or anything else. We have many different members of different ages, and we are not an adult community.

  * **Do not rip** \- Do not rip (steal) anyone’s work or designs. It is the biggest rule on all GFX sites and its just not right. You will be immediately banned and all other forums will be notified of you as a ripper.

  * **English Language** \- Please Use Only English in posts and main threads, dicussion in a second language through pms in obviously excepted however if sent to admins please check prior if they are language able.

  * **Don't insult** \- Don't insult or personally attack another member We actively discourage personal attacks on other members. You don't have the right to attack someone for having an opinion other than your own; if someone disagrees with you, they're entitled to provided they do it respectfully. If there is an issue with another member, please contact a forum moderator or administrator for help through a Private Message or an e-mail.

  * **Do not double post** \- Instead of posting twice in a row, just edit your last post and add in what you want. Your second post will be deleted.

  * **One thread** \- Do not post a thread more than once. Post a new thread in the proper forum. If the topic is relevant to more than one forum, pick the best fit or most specific forum and post it only once. Post requests in the request section, and introductions in the introduction forum, for example.

  * **Signatures** \- Signatures can only contain a maximum of two signatures and one mini-sig. Avatars can only be 100x100 in size.

  * **Don't advertise or promote** \- We delete posts that appear to be promoting or advertising products or services. Do not advertise other site, You are not allowed to use signatures that advertise other sites, Private Message (PM) advertising is strictly prohibited as well as posting topics with your website or posting in the shoutbox a link to your site.

* * *

### **Privacy Policy**

  * SportGFX recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.

  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the SportGFX web site.

  * By registering to SportGFX you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.

  * SportGFX also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general,cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as SportGFX. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)

  * SportGFX will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States legislation.

  * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.

  * You have a legal right for the personal information held at SportGFX to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.

  * SportGFX will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.

  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on SportGFX

  * This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then [Contact Us](http://sportgfx.com/forum/sendmessage/)

* * *

### **Disclaimers**

Some of the content on our site and forums, including videos, images and other resources have been collected from the Internet, or sent to us by our users. We respect the intellectual property of authors and creators and every attempt has been made to make sure that they are free use or public domain.

If you notice copyright violation on this web site, please contact the web manager and we will resolve the matter.

Of course, it is not our intention to infringe your copyright. However, we are not responsible for any errors or misuse of this information by our members.

We disclaim any responsibility for the deletion, the failure to store, the miss delivery, or the untimely delivery of any information or material.

We disclaim any responsibility for any harm resulting from downloading or accessing any information or material on the Internet using search results from our site. We disclaim any responsibility for, and if you subscribe to one of our fee-based services you will not be entitled to a refund as a result of, any service outages that are caused by our maintenance on the servers or the technology that underlies our sites, failures of our service providers (including telecommunications, hosting, and power providers), computer viruses, natural disasters or other destruction or damage of our facilities, acts of nature, war, civil disturbance, or any other cause beyond our reasonable control.

All articles posted on the SportGFX homepage (excluding images) are copyright of SportGFX or any of it’s members.

The site contains a comment system through which users may voice their opinions.

All comments opinions posted are the personal opinions of the commenter, not of  SportGFX.com. SportGFX.com will not be held responsible for any comments which are intended to damage or offence others. However, the SportGFX staff will do their best to delete unappropriate comments.
